realscout.com 2019-05-08

# RealScout - Personalized Home Search with More Data About Local Listings / RealScout

##  **Overview**

Last Updated: December 1, 2014 

This privacy policy (this “Policy”) describes the collection of personal information by RealScout, Inc., a Delaware corporation (“RealScout,” “we,” or “us”) from users of our Web site at www.RealScout.com (the “Site”), as well as all related mobile sites, applications, widgets, software, tools, and other services provided by us and on which a link to this Policy is displayed (collectively, together with the Site, our “Services”). This Policy also describes our use and disclosure of such information. By using our Services, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information in accordance with this Policy. 

## COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

### Collection of Directly-Provided Information

We collect information you provide directly to or through us. For example, we collect information when you create or update an account or profile, sign up for our newsletter, participate in any interactive features of the Services, fill out a form, send us an email, participate in a contest or promotion, subscribe to our Services, apply for a job, communicate with us via third party social media sites, request customer support, provide information to other users of the Services, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, password, postal address, phone number, credit card information, agent or broker information, BRE or other license number, demographic information, information related to properties in which you are interested, and other contact or identifying information you choose to provide. 

### Passive Information Collection

Log and Device Information: When you visit our Services, some information is collected automatically. For example, when you access our Services, we automatically collect your browser’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, information about the device from which you are visiting the Services including the nature of the device (e.g., a personal computer or a mobile device), hardware model, operating system and version, and the identifier for any handheld or mobile device that you may be using), the site(s) that you visited immediately prior to accessing the Services, the actions you take on our Services (e.g. pages viewed and access time), and the content, features, and activities that you access and participate in on our Services. We also may collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message. 

Location Information: We may collect information about the location of your mobile device when you use our mobile application or otherwise consent to the collection of this information. This information may be used for various purposes related to the Services, such as to show you listings or agents in your area. For more details about the choices you have regarding location information, please see "Your Choices" below. 

Information We Collect Through Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We may collect information passively using technologies such as standard server logs, cookies, and clear GIFs (also known as “Web beacons”). We use passively-collected information to administer, operate, and improve the Site and our other Services and systems, to understand and improve the effectiveness of advertising on our Services, to see which areas and features of our Services are popular and otherwise understand site usage, to count visits, to determine whether an email has been opened and acted upon, and to provide advertisements and other content that is tailored to you. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services. 

Third Party Advertising, Cookies, and Analytics Services. We may allow third parties, including AdRoll, Google Analytics, Inspectlet, Localytics, Segmento.io, Qualaroo, Microsoft (Bing), Crittercism.com, DelightedApp, GoToWebinar, Intercom.io, Mailchimp, Olark.com, Optimizely.com, Klaviyo.com, Sendgrid, SpyFu.com, Unbounce.com, ZenDesk.com and Primeloop.com, to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide remarketing and other analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, mobile sites and applications, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked, conversion information and other information related to the Services. This information may be used by RealScout and third parties to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online and mobile activity. For more information about Internet-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices. 

Additional Disclosures Regarding Third-Party Advertising and Analytics Services: 

Google: We may use Google Analytics, including Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Analytics for Display Advertisers or other remarketing tools, to advertise online. This enables third-party vendors, including Google, to show our ads on sites across the Internet. Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website. For information about how Google collects and processes data please see www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. For further information about Google’s privacy practices with respect to analytics, including Google’s privacy policy and various privacy controls and opt outs, please see http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html. For information on how you can opt out of Google's use of cookies for interest-based ads please visit Google's Ads Settings. 

Please note that opting out of personalized advertising through a specific analytics provider may be specific to the activities of such provider and may not affect the activities of other ad networks or analytics providers that you use. 

###  Information from Other Sources 

We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect through our Services. For example, we may collect information about you from third parties, including but not limited to real estate agents, credit bureaus, mailing list providers and publicly available sources. In addition, if you create or log into your account through a social media site, we will have access to certain information from that site, such as your name, account information and friends lists, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such social media site. 

## USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may use information about you for various purposes, including to: 

  * Provide, maintain and improve our Services;
  * Provide and deliver the information, products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices; 
  * Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;
  * Communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards, and events offered by RealScout and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you; 
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests; 
  * Process and deliver contest entries and rewards;
  * Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and 
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

## DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy: 

  * With real estate agents and other real estate service providers with whom your account is associated (e.g. who have invited you to join RealScout or with whom you have asked to be connected); 
  * With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf; 
  * In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with any applicable law, regulation or legal process, or as otherwise required by any applicable law, rule or regulation; 
  * If we believe your actions are inconsistent with the spirit or language of our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of RealScout or others; 
  * In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of RealScout assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company; and 
  * With your consent or at your direction, including if we notify you through our Services that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information. 

We may also share aggregated or anonymized information that does not directly identify you. 

The Services may offer social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook "Like" button), which let you share actions you take on our Services with other media, and vice versa. The use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features. 

## CHOICE

If you receive commercial email from us, you may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained within the email. You may also opt-out from receiving commercial email from us, and any other promotional communications that we may send to you from time to time (e.g., by postal mail) by sending your request to us by email at privacy@realscout.com or by writing to us at the address given at the end of this policy. Additionally, if we offer user account functionality on the Services, we may allow you to view and modify settings relating to the nature and frequency of promotional communications that you receive from us. 

Please be aware that if you opt-out of receiving commercial email from us, it may take up to ten business days for us to process your opt-out request, and you may receive commercial email from us during that period. Additionally, even after you opt-out from receiving commercial messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding our Services. 

When you first launch any of our mobile applications that collect location information, you will be asked to consent to the application's collection of this information. If you initially consent to our collection of location information, you can subsequently stop the collection of this information at any time by changing the preferences on your mobile device. If you do so, certain features of our Services may no longer function. 

## ACCESS

If we offer the ability to create user accounts or profiles on our Services, you may have the ability to access and update many categories of personal information that you provide to us by logging in to your account and accessing your account settings. If you wish to access or amend any other personal information we hold about you, you may contact us at privacy@realscout.com. 

If you request that we delete your account on any of our Services (via a user settings page, by email, or otherwise), we will do so within a reasonable period of time, but we may need to retain some of your information in order to satisfy our legal obligations, or where we reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so. 

## LINKS

The Services may contain links to other Web sites, products, or services that we do not own or operate. If you choose to visit or use any Third-Party Sites or products or services available on or through such Third-Party Sites, please be aware that this Policy will not apply to your activities or any information you disclose while using those Third-Party Sites or any products or services available on or through such Third-Party Sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these Third-Party Sites or any products or services on or through them. Additionally, please be aware that the Services may contain links to Web sites and services that we operate but that are governed by different privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies applicable to any Web site or service you visit other than the Services before providing any Personal Information on them. 

## INTERNATIONAL VISITORS

RealScout is based in the United States and our servers and data centers are primarily located in the United States. If you choose to use the Services from outside the U.S., then you should know that you are transferring your Personal Information outside of your region and into the U.S. for storage and processing. By providing your information to us through your use of the Services, you consent to the transfer, storage, and processing of such information in the U.S. and other countries. Also, we may transfer your data from the U.S. to other countries or regions in connection with storage and processing of data, fulfilling your requests, and operating the Services. You should know that each region can have its own privacy and data security laws, some of which may be less stringent as compared to those of your own region. 

## SECURITY

We use reasonable security measures that are designed to protect personal information from accidental loss, disclosure, misuse, and destruction. Please be aware, however, that no data security measures can be guaranteed to be completely effective. Consequently, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you provide to us. You transmit information to us at your own risk. 

## UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

We may occasionally update this Policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the beginning of the Policy. Your continued use of our Services after such changes will be subject to the then-current policy. If we change this Policy in a manner that is materially less restrictive of our use or disclosure of your information, we will use reasonable efforts to notify you of the change (such as adding a statement to our homepage, sending you an email or such other method as we determine) and to obtain your consent prior to applying the change to any information that we collected from you prior to the date the change becomes effective. We encourage you to periodically review this Policy to stay informed about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information. 

## YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California law permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at RealScout, Inc., RealScout, Inc. 144 South Whisman Drive, Ste F, Mountain View, CA 94041 or email us at privacy@realscout.com. 

##  CONTACTING US 

If you have any questions or comments about this Policy, please contact us using the following contact information: 

RealScout, Inc.   
211 Hope Street, No. 390517  
Mountain View, CA 94041
